resumel.com 2010-11-18

# Privacy Policy - Resume Templates, Sample Resume & Cover letter

Browse: [Home](http://www.resumel.com/ "ResumeL.com") / Privacy Policy 

##  [Privacy Policy](http://www.resumel.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy")

At [resumel.com](http://www.resumel.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.resumel.com and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.resumel.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Ad Servers**

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies like Google (www.google.com/adsense), Kontera, Chitika, Commission Junction, ClickBank etc. that place ads on our web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies, with the help of cookies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. Privacy Policy of Google and how to opt out of the user of DART cookie is available at [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Revision of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time without any prior notice to the visitors. Continued access of resumel.com by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. It is the goal of resumel.com to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

**Site Pages :**
